# JUAN DAVID GUERRERO JAMIOY

S O F T W A R E E N G I N E E R



**1** 0412589563

231 Waymouth St, Adelaide

m www.linkedin.com/in/juandguerreroj

# PROFILE

I am a qualified and professional software developer with 7 years of experience in back end and front end development, and project leadership. Strong creative and analytical skills. Excellent at teamworking with an eye for detail.

# SKILLS & LANGUAGES

- Front End Coding in: JavaScript,
  Angular, ReactJs
- Back End Coding in: Java, PLSQL, Nodejs, Spring boot
- Problem-Solving
- Scrum Agile methodology
- Project Management Tools
- Strong Communication
- Spanish (native)
- English (Upper-intermediate)

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **TECHNICAL ANALYST**

Codesa | May 2021 - April 2022

- Lead a backend team of a project
- Develop microservices in the backend side

## JUNIOR PROJECT MANAGER

OLSoftware | January 2021 - May 2021

- Prepare estimates for projects and develops.
- Accomplish timely monitoring and control of the project and act in case of deviations.

### SENIOR DEVELOPMENT ENGINEER

OLSoftware | November 2020 - January 2021

- Development of projects requirements.
- Accomplish the project respective documentation.

#### SENIOR IMPLEMENTATION ENGINEER

Carvajal S.A. | October 2015 - November 2020

- Implement services and support incidents.
- Application of improvements to operational processes in the human resources area

# EDUCATION

# SCRUM MASTER / SCRUM PRODUCT OWNER

CertiProf - 2021/2022

# SPECIALIST PROJECT MANAGEMENT

University San Buenaventura Cali 2020 - 2021

## **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

University Antonio José Camacho 2010 - 2015

# REFERENCES

#### **PAULA PLASTIC**

ELICOS Teacher Albright Institute Contact: 0411952422

#### MARIO CORTES

Contract Manager Quayclean Contact: 0447 243 125